<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>David Bendet</title>
    <description>Hey what&#39;s up.</description>
    <link>www.davidbendet.comwww.davidbendet.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="www.davidbendet.comwww.davidbendet.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>How many goals are scored per NHL game?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  Hey what is up.  &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 18:40:20 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>www.davidbendet.comwww.davidbendet.com/jekyll/update/2014/05/23/welcome-to-jekyll/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">www.davidbendet.comwww.davidbendet.com/jekyll/update/2014/05/23/welcome-to-jekyll/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
